
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:cc="http://cyber.law.harvard.edu/rss/creativeCommonsRssModule.html">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Psilo - Medium]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Psilocybin facts, with the goal of getting attention on it’s benefits, especially to treat depression. - Medium]]></description>
        <link>https://medium.com/psilo?source=rss----4c41534bc898---4</link>
        <image>
            <url>https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/proxy/1*MXL-j6S8fTEd8UFP_foEEw.png</url>
            <title>Psilo - Medium</title>
            <link>https://medium.com/psilo?source=rss----4c41534bc898---4</link>
        </image>
        <generator>Medium</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 21:58:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://medium.com/feed/psilo" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <webMaster><![CDATA[yourfriends@medium.com]]></webMaster>
        <atom:link href="http://medium.superfeedr.com" rel="hub"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research into psychedelics shut down for decades is now yielding exciting results]]></title>
            <link>https://medium.com/psilo/the-trip-treatment-a1e37e88ffc6?source=rss----4c41534bc898---4</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/a1e37e88ffc6</guid>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Project Psilo]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 21:22:55 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2017-05-20T19:26:55.836Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Trip Treatment: On an April Monday in 2010, Patrick Mettes, a fifty-four-year-old television news director being treated for a cancer of the bile ducts, read an article on the front page of the <em>Times</em> that would change his death. His diagnosis had come three years earlier, shortly after his wife, Lisa, noticed that the whites of his eyes had turned yellow. By 2010, the cancer had spread to Patrick’s lungs and he was buckling under the weight of a debilitating chemotherapy regimen and the growing fear that he might not survive. The article, headlined “hallucinogens have doctors tuning in again,” mentioned clinical trials at several universities, including N.Y.U., in which psilocybin — the active ingredient in so-called magic mushrooms — was being administered to cancer patients in an effort to relieve their anxiety and “existential distress.” One of the researchers was quoted as saying that, under the influence of the hallucinogen, “individuals transcend their primary identification with their bodies and experience ego-free states . . . and return with a new perspective and profound acceptance.” Patrick had never taken a psychedelic drug, but he immediately wanted to volunteer. Lisa was against the idea. “I didn’t want there to be an easy way out,” she recently told me. “I wanted him to fight.”</p><p>Patrick made the call anyway and, after filling out some forms and answering a long list of questions, was accepted into the trial. Since hallucinogens can sometimes bring to the surface latent psychological problems, researchers try to weed out volunteers at high risk by asking questions about drug use and whether there is a family history of schizophrenia or bipolar disorder. After the screening, Mettes was assigned to a therapist named Anthony Bossis, a bearded, bearish psychologist in his mid-fifties, with a specialty in palliative care. Bossis is a co-principal investigator for the N.Y.U. trial.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/690/1*aObGCEZ5jxVjE_u-_8J5vQ.png" /><figcaption>Illustration by Stephen Doyle</figcaption></figure><p>After four meetings with Bossis, Mettes was scheduled for two dosings — one of them an “active” placebo (in this case, a high dose of niacin, which can produce a tingling sensation), and the other a pill containing the psilocybin. Both sessions, Mettes was told, would take place in a room decorated to look more like a living room than like a medical office, with a comfortable couch, landscape paintings on the wall, and, on the shelves, books of art and mythology, along with various aboriginal and spiritual tchotchkes, including a Buddha and a glazed ceramic mushroom. During each session, which would last the better part of a day, Mettes would lie on the couch wearing an eye mask and listening through headphones to a carefully curated playlist — Brian Eno, Philip Glass, Pat Metheny, Ravi Shankar. Bossis and a second therapist would be there throughout, saying little but being available to help should he run into any trouble.</p><p>“I felt a little like an archeologist unearthing a completely buried body of knowledge,” he said. Beginning in the nineteen-fifties, psychedelics had been used to treat a wide variety of conditions, including alcoholism and end-of-life anxiety. The American Psychiatric Association held meetings centered on LSD. “Some of the best minds in psychiatry had seriously studied these compounds in therapeutic models, with government funding,” Ross said.</p><p>Between 1953 and 1973, the federal government spent four million dollars to fund a hundred and sixteen studies of LSD, involving more than seventeen hundred subjects. (These figures don’t include classified research.) Through the mid-nineteen-sixties, psilocybin and LSD were legal and remarkably easy to obtain. Sandoz, the Swiss chemical company where, in 1938, Albert Hofmann first synthesized LSD, gave away large quantities of Delysid — LSD — to any researcher who requested it, in the hope that someone would discover a marketable application. Psychedelics were tested on alcoholics, people struggling with obsessive-compulsive disorder, depressives, autistic children, schizophrenics, terminal cancer patients, and convicts, as well as on perfectly healthy artists and scientists (to study creativity) and divinity students (to study spirituality). The results reported were frequently positive. But many of the studies were, by modern standards, poorly designed and seldom well controlled, if at all. When there were controls, it was difficult to blind the researchers — that is, hide from them which volunteers had taken the actual drug. (This remains a problem.)</p><p>By the mid-nineteen-sixties, LSD had escaped from the laboratory and swept through the counterculture. In 1970, Richard Nixon signed the Controlled Substances Act and put most psychedelics on Schedule 1, prohibiting their use for any purpose. Research soon came to a halt, and what had been learned was all but erased from the field of psychiatry. “By the time I got to medical school, no one even talked about it,” Ross said.</p><p>Source =&gt; <a href="http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2015/02/09/trip-treatment">here</a></p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=a1e37e88ffc6" width="1" height="1"><hr><p><a href="https://medium.com/psilo/the-trip-treatment-a1e37e88ffc6">Research into psychedelics shut down for decades is now yielding exciting results</a> was originally published in <a href="https://medium.com/psilo">Psilo</a> on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New study shows magic mushrooms repair brain damage caused by extreme trauma]]></title>
            <link>https://medium.com/psilo/new-study-shows-magic-mushrooms-repair-brain-damage-caused-by-extreme-trauma-26b04238dcce?source=rss----4c41534bc898---4</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/26b04238dcce</guid>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Project Psilo]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 17:20:37 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2017-05-20T18:31:04.609Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new study by The University of South Florida has found that low doses of the active ingredient in magic mushrooms repairs brain damage caused by extreme trauma, offering renewed hope to millions of sufferers of PTSD (Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder).</p><p>The study confirms previous research by Imperial College London, that psilocybin, a naturally occurring compound present in “shrooms”, stimulates new brain cell growth and erases frightening memories. Mice conditioned to fear electric shock when hearing a noise associated with the shock “simply lost their fear”, says Dr. Juan Sanchez-Ramos, who co-authored the study. A low dose of psilocybin led them to overcome “fear conditioning” and the freeze response associated with it faster than the group of mice on Ketanserin (a drug that counteracts the receptor that binds psilocybin in the brain) and a control group on saline.</p><p>An estimated 5 percent of Americans — more than 13 million people — have PTSD at any given time, according to the PTSD Alliance. The condition more often associated with combat veterans, is twice as likely to develop in women because they tend to experience interpersonal violence (such as domestic violence, rape and abuse) more often than men.</p><h3>Decriminalization of psilocybin could help millions</h3><p>Previous studies have shown that low doses of psilocybin produce no consciousness state altering effects. Administered in the correct amount, psilocybin could therefore be assumed to safely treat PTSD with minimal risk of adverse side effects. Magic mushrooms could help millions recover from the debilitating cycles of fight and flight and other conditioned biological responses caused by extreme trauma, if only they weren’t listed as a dangerous Schedule 1 drug with no medical benefits.</p><p>Meanwhile, doctors are authorised to dispense powerful, side-effect laden pharmaceutical drugs to army vets and others suffering from the symptoms of PTSD without any evidence that these treatments actually work, according to a major review by the committee of the Institute of Medicine on the topic.</p><p>The situation is so bad that an average of 18 American veterans commits suicide every day, linked to the sharp rise in prescription drugs, depression, and other psychological conditions. Safe, natural alternatives to pharmaceuticals such as homeopathic and herbal remedies have been found to alleviate symptoms. Meditation has also been shown to reduce high activity levels in the amygdala (the brain’s emotional centre) experienced in PTSD sufferers as anxiety, stress and phobias.</p><p>Source =&gt; <a href="http://www.naturalnews.com/041393_psilocybin_psychological_disorders_magic_mushrooms.html">here</a></p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=26b04238dcce" width="1" height="1"><hr><p><a href="https://medium.com/psilo/new-study-shows-magic-mushrooms-repair-brain-damage-caused-by-extreme-trauma-26b04238dcce">New study shows magic mushrooms repair brain damage caused by extreme trauma</a> was originally published in <a href="https://medium.com/psilo">Psilo</a> on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Takeaways from Psilocybin for anxiety and depression in cancer care]]></title>
            <link>https://medium.com/psilo/takeaways-from-psilocybin-for-anxiety-and-depression-in-cancer-care-7884a2d16f1f?source=rss----4c41534bc898---4</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/7884a2d16f1f</guid>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Project Psilo]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 15:59:59 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2017-05-20T18:40:37.534Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Editorial by David Nutt from the special Psilocybin issue of the Journal of Psychopharmacology vol 30, 2016.</p><p>This special issue of the Journal of Psychopharmacology contains two landmark studies — the most rigorous controlled trials to date using the psychedelic drug psilocybin, the active ingredient of magic mushrooms (Griffiths et al., 2016; Ross et al., 2016). These were conducted in patients with anxiety and depression and existential distress in the context of having a diagnosis of cancer, and they showed that a single psychedelic experience could produce profound and enduring mental health benefits.</p><p>To many people brought up in the Reagan drug war era with the ‘drugs fry your brain’ message, psilocybin may seem a strange and possibly even a dangerous drug treatment of serious mental illness. For this reason, we have asked a number of significant figures in relevant research areas to provide commentaries on the two studies. These experts in the fields of psychiatry, trial design and end-of-life care provide their perspective on the research and its implications for clinical practice. The fact that everyone we approached agreed to provide a commentary, despite short notice, is a testimony to the interest that these two studies have sparked.</p><p>When Albert Hoffman discovered the remarkable mind-altering properties of lysergic acid diethylamide (LSD) in 1943, he didn’t have much trouble persuading his bosses at the pharmaceutical company Sandoz (now part of Novartis) that this drug would play a very important role in understanding the nature of mental illness and potentially providing a very novel approach to their treatment. Through the 1950s and 1960s, Sandoz supplied medical LSD in the form of Delysid that was studied in hundreds of trials in thousands of patients. The US government via the National Institutes of Health funded more than 130 grants in this field. Results were generally reported as positive and encouraging in disorders including anxiety, depression and addiction (Krebs and Johansen, 2012). One of the founders of Alcoholics Anonymous, Bill Wilson, was so impressed by the power of LSD to change alcoholics’ defeatist focus on alcohol and to give them insights into powers beyond themselves that he encouraged treatment research with it.</p><p>Unfortunately, psilocybin got caught up in the backlash against LSD occasioned by the protests against the Vietnam War and the Haight–Ashbury social revolution. So when LSD was banned on the basis of some very dubious so-called research findings of harm, psilocybin and all other known psychedelic drugs became illegal too. There was no evidence of psilocybin being harmful enough to be controlled when it was banned, and since then, it has continued to be used safely by millions of young people worldwide with a very low incidence of problems. In a number of countries, it has remained legal, for example in Mexico where all plant products are legal, and in Holland where the underground bodies of the mushrooms (so-called truffles) were exempted from control.</p><p>It is the safety and ease of practical use of psilocybin that has led to it being resurrected in a series of psychological (Griffiths et al., 2006, 2008, 2011), psychopharmacological (Kometer et al., 2012; Pokorny et al., 2016; Vollenweider et al., 1998), imaging (Carhart-Harris, Erritzoe, et al., 2012a; Carhart-Harris, Leech, et al., 2012b; Carhart-Harris et al., 2013) and small pilot clinical studies (Bogenschutz et al., 2015; Carhart-Harris et al., 2016; Grob et al., 2011; Johnson et al., 2014; Moreno et al., 2006). These have provided the intellectual and safety data underpinning the two current studies that are special in that they are the most rigorous double-blind placebo-controlled trials of a psychedelic drug in the past 50 years. Hopefully, the positive findings that they report will act to spur on other researchers in the field of psychopharmacology, particularly in relation to depression, anxiety and addiction — disorders of enormous personal and social costs, and with many patients who still fail to respond adequately to current treatments, as well as to patients with existential distress.</p><p>Source =&gt; <a href="http://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/0269881116675754">here</a></p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=7884a2d16f1f" width="1" height="1"><hr><p><a href="https://medium.com/psilo/takeaways-from-psilocybin-for-anxiety-and-depression-in-cancer-care-7884a2d16f1f">Takeaways from Psilocybin for anxiety and depression in cancer care</a> was originally published in <a href="https://medium.com/psilo">Psilo</a> on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid and sustained symptom reduction following psilocybin treatment for anxiety and depression]]></title>
            <link>https://medium.com/psilo/rapid-and-sustained-symptom-reduction-following-psilocybin-treatment-for-anxiety-and-depression-in-d99a0b3352cd?source=rss----4c41534bc898---4</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/d99a0b3352cd</guid>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Project Psilo]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 15:50:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2017-05-20T19:03:04.228Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First study from the December 2016 special Psilocybin issue of the Journal of Psychopharmacology, by Ross et al (with great thanks to all the authors)</p><h3>Summary of psilocybin</h3><p>Psilocybin, a tryptamine serotoninergic psychedelic, exerts its consciousness altering effects via 5HT2A agonism (Vollenweider and Kometer, 2010). It has a well-established physiological and psychological safety profile in human laboratory and clinical trial research (Johnson et al., 2008), is not known to be addictive and may have anti-addictive properties (Bogenschutz and Johnson, 2016; Krebs and Johansen, 2012; Ross, 2012). It can produce highly salient spiritual/mystical states of consciousness associated with enduring (months to years) positive changes in cognition, affect, behavior, and spirituality (Doblin, 1991; Griffiths et al., 2006, 2008, 2011; Pahnke, 1963).</p><p>Unfortunately, psilocybin got caught up in the backlash against LSD occasioned by the protests against the Vietnam War and the Haight–Ashbury social revolution. So when LSD was banned on the basis of some very dubious so-called research findings of harm, psilocybin and all other known psychedelic drugs became illegal too. There was no evidence of psilocybin being harmful enough to be controlled when it was banned, and since then, it has continued to be used safely by millions of young people worldwide with a very low incidence of problems. In a number of countries, it has remained legal, for example in Mexico where all plant products are legal, and in Holland where the underground bodies of the mushrooms (so-called truffles) were exempted from control.</p><h3>Adverse effects</h3><p>In terms of AEs attributable to psilocybin, the most common medical AEs were non-clinically significant elevations in BP and HR (76%), headaches/migraines (28%), and nausea (14%); the most common psychiatric AEs were transient anxiety (17%) and transient psychotic-like symptoms (7%: one case of transient paranoid ideation and one case of transient thought disorder). The medical AEs (non-clinically significant elevations in BP and HR, head- aches, nausea), and psychiatric AEs (transient anxiety, transient near-psychotic symptoms) attributable to psilocybin are all known AEs of psilocybin, were transient, tolerable, and consistent with prior trials of psilocybin administration in normal volunteers (Griffiths et al., 2006, 2008, 2011), and patients with terminal cancer (Grob et al., 2011).</p><h3>Positive effects</h3><p>For all primary outcome measures, the psilocybin first group demonstrated significant within-group reductions (compared to baseline at each post-baseline assessment point) in anxiety and depression immediately after receiving psilocybin. These reductions remained significant at each time point, including the final point at 26 weeks post-dose 2 (approximately 8 months), post-psilocybin dosing.</p><p>In the short-term (2 weeks post- dose 1), psilocybin (compared to control) produced decreases in cancer-related demoralization and hopelessness, while improving spiritual wellbeing and quality of life (physical, psychological, environmental domains). These effects were sustained at the final 6.5 month follow-up. Regarding anxiety and attitudes towards death, the data were mixed. In the short-term (2 weeks post-dose 1), psilocybin was not significantly associated with decreased death anxiety or increased death transcendence. However, at the 26-week post-dose 2 final follow-up assessment, while death anxiety (as measured by the DAS) continued to demonstrate no significant reductions, there was a significant improvement in attitudes and adaptations towards death (as measured by the DTS) in the psilocybin first group compared to the niacin first group (assessed at 2 weeks post-dose 1).</p><p>As shown, prior to the crossover, psilocybin produced significantly greater ratings (compared to the niacin first group assessed at 2 weeks post-dose 1) of positive persisting effects on: attitudes about life and self, mood changes, social effects (e.g. increased altruism), behavior, and spirituality. After the crossover, these effects were sustained at the final 6.5-month follow-up. When all participants were asked (26 weeks post-session 2) to reflect on what they thought was their psilocybin session, 52% and 70% rated the psilocybin experience as the singular or top 5 most spiritually significant, or the singular or top 5 most personally meaningful experience of their entire lives, respectively; while 87% reported increased life satisfaction or wellbeing attributed to the experience.</p><p>Psilocybin was associated with substantial anti-depressant response rates (as high as approximately 80% at 6.5 months follow-up).</p><p>Psilocybin decreased cancer-related demoralization (e.g. loss of meaning/hope/purpose, desire for hastened death) and hopelessness, while improving spiritual wellbeing, general life satisfaction, and quality of life.</p><p>Psilocybin experiences were reported as highly meaningful and spiritual, and associated with positive cognitive, affective, spiritual, and behavioral effects lasting weeks to months. This finding is consistent with prior research administering psilocybin to normal volunteers (Doblin, 1991; Griffiths et al., 2006, 2008, 2011; Pahnke, 1963).</p><h3>Conclusion</h3><p>In conclusion, single moderate-dose psilocybin (in conjunction with psychotherapy) was safely administered to a cohort of patients with cancer-related psychological distress (e.g. anxiety, depression). It produced rapid and sustained anxiolytic and anti-depressant effects (for at least 7 weeks but potentially as long as 8 months), decreased cancer-related existential dis- tress, increased spiritual wellbeing and quality of life, and was associated with improved attitudes towards death. The psilocybin-induced mystical experience mediated the anxiolytic and anti-depressant effects of psilocybin.</p><p>Source =&gt; <a href="http://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/0269881116675512">here</a></p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=d99a0b3352cd" width="1" height="1"><hr><p><a href="https://medium.com/psilo/rapid-and-sustained-symptom-reduction-following-psilocybin-treatment-for-anxiety-and-depression-in-d99a0b3352cd">Rapid and sustained symptom reduction following psilocybin treatment for anxiety and depression</a> was originally published in <a href="https://medium.com/psilo">Psilo</a> on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psilocybin Actually Inhibits The Processing Of Negative Emotions In The Brain]]></title>
            <link>https://medium.com/psilo/psilocybin-actually-inhibits-the-processing-of-negative-emotions-in-the-brain-fbc34c6c0577?source=rss----4c41534bc898---4</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/fbc34c6c0577</guid>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Project Psilo]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 13:21:58 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2017-05-20T18:27:47.817Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Psilocybin is known for captivating its imbiber with novel thought and emotional surrender. These mystical experiences can be powerful enough to affect one’s perception and leave an imprint on their outlook that can last from days to weeks to even months. People have also reported experiencing a powerful alleviation of psychiatric ailments such as depression, anxiety, OCD, and ADHD. The testimonies alone show that psilocybin has true therapeutic value in the psychiatric field. What is it that happens to the mind in order to instill it with the improved outlook and mental clarity?</p><p>Researchers at the Psychiatric University Hospital of Zurich are now looking into psilocybin’s effect on the amygdala, a key component of the brain’s ability to process emotions. The amygdala, located at the beginning of the brain stem, can often become overactive leading one into constant depressive thinking, distraction, anxiety and so on. “Elevated activity of the amygdala in response to stimuli leads to the neurons strengthening negative signals and weakening the processing of positive ones. This mechanism plays an important role in the development of depression and anxiety disorders.” — UZH Research</p><p>The ‘goal’ of pharmaceutical anti-depressants and anti-anxiety medications is to inhibit brain activity that leads to negativity and fear. Unfortunately, these medications really only serve as a band-aid and sadly, can even amplify the problem if someone is to become dependent and then abstain. They can negatively impact serotonin, a natural neurotransmitter that contributes to happiness and well being. On the other hand, researchers recognize now that the compound psilocybin is effective in temporarily decreasing activity in the amygdala, allowing it an opportunity to recover from an over active state while promoting the health of serotonin transmitters. “Psilocybin positively influences mood in healthy individuals. In the brain, this substance stimulates specific docking sites for the messenger serotonin. The scientists therefore assumed that psilocybin exerts its mood-brightening effect via a change in the serotonin system in the limbic brain regions.” — UZH Research</p><p>Now, researchers are formulating news studies to understand more about the relationship between psilocybin and mental illness. Knowing that overactivity of the amygdala leads to depressive thinking and that psilocybin has the capacity to correct this problem, researchers believe that the compound will one day be prized for its medicinal capabilities. The fact that some on can feel relief from such terrible burdens with one session of psilocybin therapy rather than daily intake of medications is ground breaking. Psilocybin, among other sacred medicines, have been present in some of the most ancestral indigenous cultures of the world, and now western medicine is just barely understanding the truth of these medicines and their many uses. The potential of these primordial medicines that humanity has been neglecting may be the key to the understanding and treatment of all mental illness, thus opening the door to a long forgotten form of healing.</p><p>Source =&gt; <a href="https://medium.com/@HighEscapade/psilocybin-actually-inhibits-the-processing-of-negative-emotions-in-the-brain-405849275ab2#.niu7rluyu">here</a></p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=fbc34c6c0577" width="1" height="1"><hr><p><a href="https://medium.com/psilo/psilocybin-actually-inhibits-the-processing-of-negative-emotions-in-the-brain-fbc34c6c0577">Psilocybin Actually Inhibits The Processing Of Negative Emotions In The Brain</a> was originally published in <a href="https://medium.com/psilo">Psilo</a> on Medium, where people are continuing the conversation by highlighting and responding to this story.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
